[
    {
        "question": "Which of the following predatory mammals has the strongest bite force?",
        "answer_one": "Polar Bear",
        "answer_two": "Jaguar",
        "answer_three": "Bengal Tiger",
        "answer_four": "Grizzly Bear",
        "correct_answer": "Jaguar",
        "user_id": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was the only member of the cast of Lord of the Rings to meet the author J.R.R. Tolkien?",
        "answer_one": "Christopher Lee",
        "answer_two": "Ian McKellen",
        "answer_three": "Viggo Mortenson",
        "answer_four": "Hugo Weaving",
        "correct_answer": "Christopher Lee",
        "user_id": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "English football player Lee Todd famously received a red card in two seconds for:",
        "answer_one": "Foul language",
        "answer_two": "Striking a player",
        "answer_three": "Spitting on a player",
        "answer_four": "Interfering with a penalty",
        "correct_answer": "Foul language",
        "user_id": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "In Norse Mythology which god is prophecised to slay the trickster Loki at Ragnarok?",
        "answer_one": "Thor",
        "answer_two": "Odin",
        "answer_three": "Tyr",
        "answer_four": "Heimdall",
        "correct_answer": "Heimdall",
        "user_id": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is widely considered to be the first Marvel superhero, first appearing in Marvel Comics issue 1?",
        "answer_one": "Captain America",
        "answer_two": "The Human Torch",
        "answer_three": "Namor the Sub-Mariner",
        "answer_four": "Black Widow",
        "correct_answer": "The Human Torch",
        "user_id": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "What day was this entry made?",
        "answer_one": "Monday",
        "answer_two": "Tuesday",
        "answer_three": "Wednesday",
        "answer_four": "Thursday",
        "correct_answer": "Wednesday",
        "user_id": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the first movie ever created by Disney?",
        "answer_one": "Cinderella",
        "answer_two": "Snow White and the Seven Dwarves",
        "answer_three": "Pinocchio",
        "answer_four": "Bambi",
        "correct_answer": "Snow White and the Seven Dwarves",
        "user_id": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "What planet in our solar system is the hottest?",
        "answer_one": "Mars",
        "answer_two": "Mercury",
        "answer_three": "Venus",
        "answer_four": "Jupiter",
        "correct_answer": "Venus",
        "user_id": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Bird was the nickname of which famous jazz saxophonist?",
        "answer_one": "Sonny Rollins",
        "answer_two": "John Coltrane",
        "answer_three": "Charlie Parker",
        "answer_four": "Dexter Gordon",
        "correct_answer": "Charlie Parker",
        "user_id": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the largest country in Africa by area?",
        "answer_one": "Algeria",
        "answer_two": "Kenya",
        "answer_three": "Libya",
        "answer_four": "Egypt",
        "correct_answer": "Algeria",
        "user_id": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "WiFi was invented in which country?",
        "answer_one": "USA",
        "answer_two": "Canada",
        "answer_three": "Australia",
        "answer_four": "Germany",
        "correct_answer": "Australia",
        "user_id": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Saturn is the Roman equivilant of which Greek Mythological figure?",
        "answer_one": "Hephaestus",
        "answer_two": "Hermes",
        "answer_three": "Thanatos",
        "answer_four": "Kronos",
        "correct_answer": "Kronos",
        "user_id": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Which African animal holds the nickname of the widowmaker?",
        "answer_one": "Lion",
        "answer_two": "Cape Buffalo",
        "answer_three": "Hippo",
        "answer_four": "Elephant",
        "correct_answer": "Cape Buffalo",
        "user_id": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sport did former US president Abraham Lincoln a champion in?",
        "answer_one": "Fencing",
        "answer_two": "Javelin",
        "answer_three": "Boxing",
        "answer_four": "Wrestling",
        "correct_answer": "Wrestling",
        "user_id": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was the author of the novel Jurassic Park?",
        "answer_one": "Robert Jordan",
        "answer_two": "Brandon Sanderson",
        "answer_three": "Michael Crichton",
        "answer_four": "Terry Goodkind",
        "correct_answer": "Michael Crichton",
        "user_id": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "The TV show Supernatural had a record-breaking run, airing a total of:",
        "answer_one": "319 episodes",
        "answer_two": "327 episodes",
        "answer_three": "333 episodes",
        "answer_four": "340 episodes",
        "correct_answer": "327 episodes",
        "user_id": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Which metal on the periodic table has the atomic symbol Sn?",
        "answer_one": "Gold",
        "answer_two": "Lead",
        "answer_three": "Iron",
        "answer_four": "Tin",
        "correct_answer": "Tin",
        "user_id": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "The Egyptian god Horus was said to have the head of which animal?",
        "answer_one": "Falcon",
        "answer_two": "Cat",
        "answer_three": "Lion",
        "answer_four": "Crocodile",
        "correct_answer": "Falcon",
        "user_id": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the capital city of Canada?",
        "answer_one": "Toronto",
        "answer_two": "Quebec",
        "answer_three": "Ottowa",
        "answer_four": "Vancouver",
        "correct_answer": "Ottowa",
        "user_id": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "How many players are required in a team for field hockey?",
        "answer_one": "7",
        "answer_two": "9",
        "answer_three": "11",
        "answer_four": "13",
        "correct_answer": "11",
        "user_id": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Which world-famous strongman was the first person successfully to deadlift 500kg?",
        "answer_one": "Brian Shaw",
        "answer_two": "Hafthor Bjornsson",
        "answer_three": "Robert Oberst",
        "answer_four": "Eddie Hall",
        "correct_answer": "Eddie Hall",
        "user_id": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "In which country was LEGO invented?",
        "answer_one": "Denmark",
        "answer_two": "Sweden",
        "answer_three": "Hungary",
        "answer_four": "Russia",
        "correct_answer": "Denmark",
        "user_id": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the first monster to ever do battle with Godzilla in a movie?",
        "answer_one": "King Kong",
        "answer_two": "Anguirus",
        "answer_three": "Mothra",
        "answer_four": "Rodan",
        "correct_answer": "Anguirus",
        "user_id": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the first story published by author H.P. Lovecraft?",
        "answer_one": "The Tomb",
        "answer_two": "Dagon",
        "answer_three": "Polaris",
        "answer_four": "The Alchemist",
        "correct_answer": "The Alchemist",
        "user_id": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "What of the following days of the week was not named after a Norse god?",
        "answer_one": "Wednesday",
        "answer_two": "Thursday",
        "answer_three": "Friday",
        "answer_four": "Saturday",
        "correct_answer": "Saturday",
        "user_id": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "What colour is a polar bear's skin?",
        "answer_one": "White",
        "answer_two": "Pink",
        "answer_three": "Grey",
        "answer_four": "Black",
        "correct_answer": "Black",
        "user_id": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Due to theraml expansion, the Eiffel Tower can grow in summer by a height of:",
        "answer_one": "10cm",
        "answer_two": "12cm",
        "answer_three": "15cm",
        "answer_four": "20cm",
        "correct_answer": "15cm",
        "user_id": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "What word is used to describe a group of alligators?",
        "answer_one": "Gang",
        "answer_two": "Troupe",
        "answer_three": "Coalition",
        "answer_four": "Congregation",
        "correct_answer": "Congregation",
        "user_id": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Keith Moon was the drummer of which famous band?",
        "answer_one": "Cream",
        "answer_two": "The Yardbirds",
        "answer_three": "The Who",
        "answer_four": "The Rolling Stones",
        "correct_answer": "Congregation",
        "user_id": 3
    }
]